<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>What&#39;s New on Buddhist Study Association of IU</title>
    <link>https://example.com/updates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in What&#39;s New on Buddhist Study Association of IU</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 12:21:57 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://example.com/updates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-09</title>
      <link>https://example.com/updates/2020-09-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/updates/2020-09-08/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone,
I hope you&amp;rsquo;re settling into your class schedules by now and managing to stay healthy.
This Friday (the 11th), we will hold our regular 6:30-7:00 p.m. meditation period outside and in person. We will meet at the IU Tailgate Field at the corner of N Fess Ave. and E 14th St. If you put &amp;ldquo;IU Tailgate Field&amp;rdquo; into Google Maps you should be able to find directions to it; it is just south of the football stadium.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-09-04</title>
      <link>https://example.com/updates/2020-09-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/updates/2020-09-04/</guid>
      <description>Hi all,
Just a quick reminder that the Buddhist Study Association&amp;rsquo;s call out meeting will be tonight at 7:15 pm. We&amp;rsquo;ll explain what kind of activities we will offer this semester and also see if we can come up with some new ideas for this strange semester online. The meeting link is: https://zoom.us/j/848430025.
We will also be having meditation tonight as usual from 6:30 to 7:00 pm. It will take place at the same link above.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-08-31</title>
      <link>https://example.com/updates/2020-08-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/updates/2020-08-31/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone,
Thanks to all of you who dropped in during the virtual involvement fair last week. It was nice meeting you all! Also, if you just signed up to receive e-mails from us in the past few days, we look forward to seeing you soon!
This Friday (September 4th) at 7:15 p.m. (after meditation) we will have a call out meeting for those looking for more information about the group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-08-26</title>
      <link>https://example.com/updates/2020-08-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/updates/2020-08-26/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone,
For those of you who showed up to meditation on Monday, I mentioned that we had a different link for meditation on Wednesday. We have simplified and we are now using the same link for the 6:30-7:00 pm meditation every weekday. The link is the same as the one that I sent in the previous e-mail, but it now works for Wednesday evenings too (https://zoom.us/j/848430025).
There is also a book discussion group with people from the Sanshin Zen Community in town that follows the Wednesday evening Zoom meditation (but you certainly don&amp;rsquo;t need to stay for it if you just want to come to meditation).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcomd Back</title>
      <link>https://example.com/updates/2020-08-24-welcom-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/updates/2020-08-24-welcom-back/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone,
Welcome back! I hope everyone and their families have managed to stay safe and healthy. This semester will be a bit bizarre, both generally and for the Buddhist Study Association (BSA) as well, due to the pandemic. It&amp;rsquo;s likely that all of our events will be online, but I will do what I can to explore possibilities to meet in person safely.
For those of you who have never participated with the Buddhist Study Association before, the following should give you a sense of what we have to offer:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>